Prints and Printing Photograph Collection
Yale University Arts Library
- Prints. (Box 3)
  - Non-Asian., 3275 (Box 7)
    - United States., 732 (Box 40)
      - Known artists., 715 (Box 40)
        - Miscellaneous M-Q., 43 (Box 45)
          - Maurer, Louis, 1832-1932., 1 (Box 45)
          - Mead, Roderick, 1900-., 1 (Box 45)
          - Miller, K. H., 1876-., 1 (Box 45)
          - Morehead, Scipio, XVIII C., 1 (Box 45)
          - Morris, Kyle, 1918-., 1 (Box 45)
          - Motherwell, Robert, 1915-., 3 (Box 45)
          - Moy, Semong, XX C., 1 (Box 45)
          - Myers, Malcolm, XX C., 1 (Box 45)
          - Nason, Thomas W., 1889-., 1 (Box 45)
          - Newsam, Albert, 1809-1864., 1 (Box 45)
          - Norman, Da Loria, 1872-1935., 1 (Box 45)
          - Norman, J., XVIII C.?, 1 (Box 45)
          - Oakford, Ellen, XIX-XX C., 1 (Box 45)
          - O'Hara, Frederick, XX C., 1 (Box 45)
          - Orr, Louis, 1889-., 1 (Box 45)
          - Ossorio, Alfonso, 1916-., 1 (Box 45)
          - Palmer, Francis, c.1812-1876., 2 (Box 45)
          - Peale, Charles Wilson, 1741-1827., 3 (Box 45)
          - Pearlstein, Philip, 1924-., 2 (Box 45)
          - Peets, Orville Houghton, 1884-., 1 (Box 45)
          - Peirce, Waldo, 1884-1970., 2 (Box 45)
          - Pelham, Henry, 1749-1806., 1 (Box 45)
          - Pelham, Peter, 1684-1751., 3 (Box 45)
          - Peltro, John, 1760-1808., 1 (Box 45)
          - Pierce, Leona, XX C., 1 (Box 45)
          - Pozzatti, Rudy O., 1925-., 2 (Box 45)
          - Prang, Louis, XIX C., 1 (Box 45)
          - Prendergast, Maurice, 1859-1924., 2 (Box 45)
          - Quastler, Gertrude, XX C., 1 (Box 45)
        - Individual artists, M-Q., 39 (Box 46)
          - Margo, Boris, 1902., 4 (Box 46)
          - Marin, John, 1870-1953., 2 (Box 46)
          - Marsh, Reginald, 1898-1954., 13 (Box 46)
          - Peale, Rembrandt, 1778-1860., 4 (Box 46)
          - Pennell, Joseph, 1860-1926., 16 (Box 46)
        - Miscellaneous artists, R-Z., 75 (Box 46)
          - Raleigh, Henry, 1880-., 2 (Box 46)
          - Rattner, Abraham, 1893-., 1 (Box 46)
          - Reason, Patrick, XIX C., 2 (Box 46)
          - Reder, Bernard, XX C., 1 (Box 46)
          - Remington, Frederic, 1861-1909., 2 (Box 46)
          - Robinson, Boardman, 1876-., 2 (Box 46)
          - Rollinson, William, XVIII-XIX C., 1 (Box 46)
          - Roth, Ernest D., XIX-XX C., 1 (Box 46)
          - Rothenberg, Susan, 1945-., 1 (Box 46)
          - Ruscha, Edward, 1937-., 2 (Box 46)
          - Ruzicka, Rudolph, 1883-., 2 (Box 46)
          - Samaras, Lucas, 1936-., 1 (Box 46)
          - Sarony and Major, XIX C., 1 (Box 46)
          - Scacki, Francisco, XIX C., 1 (Box 46)
          - Schwartz, Aubrey, XX C., 1 (Box 46)
          - Shahn, Ben, 1898-., 2 (Box 46)
          - Sheeler, Charles, 1883-., 2 (Box 46)
          - Soyer, Raphael, 1899-., 1 (Box 46)
          - Spencer, Niles, 1893-1952., 1 (Box 46)
          - Spruance, Benton, XX C., 2 (Box 46)
          - Stanton, Blair Hughes, XX C., 1 (Box 46)
          - Steg, James, XX C., 1 (Box 46)
          - Steir, Pat, XX C., 1 (Box 46)
          - Sterner, Albert, 1863-., 2 (Box 46)
          - Strang, William, 1859-1921., 1 (Box 46)
          - Tait, Arthur, 1819-1905., 3 (Box 46)
          - Thiebaud, Wayne, 1920-., 2 (Box 46)
          - Tiebot, Cornelius, c.1777-1830., 1 (Box 46)
          - Tobey, Mark, 1890-., 1 (Box 46)
          - Townsend, Lee, 1895-., 1 (Box 46)
          - Travis, Paul Bough, XX C., 1 (Box 46)
          - Trova, Ernest, 1927-., 3 (Box 46)
          - Tuttle, H. Emerson, 1890-., 2 (Box 46)
          - Twombly, Cy, 1929-., 2 (Box 47)
          - Varin, R., XIX C., 1 (Box 47)
          - Warhol, Andy, 1930-1987., 1 (Box 47)
          - Webster, Herman A., XIX-XX C., 2 (Box 47)
          - Weir, J. Alden, 1852-1919., 2 (Box 47)
          - Wengenroth, S., 1906-., 1 (Box 47)
          - Wesselmann, Tom, 1931-., 1 (Box 47)
          - West, Levon, 1900-., 2 (Box 47)
          - Westerman, Horace C., 1922-1981., 1 (Box 47)
          - Wickey, Harry, 1892-., 3 (Box 47)
          - Wilcox, Frank N., XX C., 1 (Box 47)
          - Woodbury, Charles H., XX C., 1 (Box 47)
          - Woollett, William, XX C., 1 (Box 47)
          - Young, Mahonri, 1877-., 2 (Box 47)
          - Zorach, William, 1887-., 1 (Box 47)
          - Zucker, Joe, 1941-., 1 (Box 47)
        - Individual artists, R-Z., 132 (Box 47)
          - Rauschenberg, Robert, 1925-., 24 (Box 47)
          - Revere, Paul, 1735-1818., 7 (Box 47)
          - Rosenquist, James, 1933-., 4 (Box 47)
          - Savage, Edward, 1761-1817., 9 (Box 47)
          - Sloan, John, 1871-1951., 9 (Box 47)
          - Stella, Frank, 1936-., 5 (Box 47)
          - Tanner, Benjamin, 1775-1848., 3 (Box 47)
          - Trumbull, John, 1756-1843., 4 (Box 48)
          - West, Benjamin, 1738-1820., 5 (Box 48)
          - Whistler, James McNeil, 1834-1903., 56 (Box 48)
          - Wood, Grant, 1892-1942., 6 (Box 48)
- Processes., 26 (Box 49)
  - Engraving., 5 (Box 49)
  - Etching., 6 (Box 49)
  - Mezzotint., 1 (Box 49)
  - Photographs., 2 (Box 49)
  - Printing., 12 (Box 49)